A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Accessions 1982-2004 FA1101
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Accessions 1982-2004
1953-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University Press
Rockefeller University.
FA1101
204.36 Cubic Feet 156 standard record storage boxes
Other Finding Aids note
For other Journal of General Physiology records currently open for research see:
FA925 Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Editorial Correspondence, Series 2.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 25 years old are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 517-U
Arrangement
Arranged in two series:
Series 1: Manuscripts.Series 2: Correspondence Concerning Manuscripts.
Scope and Contents
Contains manuscripts and associated correspondence concerning manuscripts, including general correspondence as well as editorial correspondence.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to RAC as 15 accessions during the period 1982-2004.
Accesions include but are not limited to: 1984:109, 1984:112, 1984:116, 1984:120, 1984:125, 1984:131, 1984:135, 1984:139, 1990:048, 1994:049, 1995:023, 1995:026, 1995:027, 1997;096, 2004:051, as well as several transfers in 1982.
- Manuscripts, 1965-1996; 1
  - 1665 - 1947 (Box 1)
  - 1858 - 1997 (Box 2)
  - 2000-2085, 3009-3037 (Box 3)
  - 3107 - 3230 (Box 4)
  - 3231 - 3330 (Box 5)
  - 2089 - 3259 (Box 6)
  - 3260 - 3448 (Box 7)
  - 2095, 3120-3137, 3427, 3450-3523 (Box 8)
  - 3038-3102, 3235, 3400-3405, 3524-3593 (Box 9)
  - 3016 - 3044 (Box 30)
  - 3406-3439, 3481-3494, 3539-3566, 3600-3642 (Box 10)
  - 3593 - 3695 (Box 33)
  - 3696 - 3828, 3181 (Box 34)
  - 3645-3680, 3737-3789 (Box 11)
  - 3791 - 3896 (Box 12)
  - 3897 - 3954 (Box 13)
  - 3951 - 3996 (Box 14)
  - 3998 - 4067 (Box 15)
  - 4068 - 4134 (Box 16)
  - 4135 - 4195 (Box 17)
  - 4198 - 4287 (Box 18)
  - 4294 - 4354 (Box 19)
  - 4355 - 4408 (Box 20)
  - 4409 - 4458 (Box 21)
  - 4462 - 4499 (Box 22)
  - 4500 - 4540 (Box 23)
  - 4541 - 4588 (Box 24)
  - 4584, 4589-4622 (Box 25)
  - 4622 - 4670 (Box 26)
  - 4670 - 4727 (Box 27)
  - 4731 - 4785 (Box 28)
  - 4786 - 4830 (Box 29)
  - 4834 - 4856 (Box 30)
  - 4856 - 4920 (Box 31)
  - 4808, 4922-4968 (Box 32)
  - 4870 - 4999 (Box 33)
  - 5001 - 5009 (Box 34)
  - 5009 - 5046 (Box 35)
  - 5049 - 5088 (Box 36)
  - 5090 - 5122 (Box 37)
  - 5124 - 5161 (Box 38)
  - 5131 - 5132 (Box 41)
  - 5162 - 5209, 1982-1983 (Box 39)
  - 5210 - 5265, 1982-1983 (Box 40)
  - 5266 - 5299, 1982-1983 (Box 41)
  - 5133, 5211, 5251, 5253, 5275, 5276, 1982-1983 (Box 42)
  - 5307 - 5346, 1982-1983 (Box 42)
  - 5347 - 5383, 1982-1983 (Box 43)
  - 5384 - 5429, 1982-1983 (Box 44)
  - 5429 - 5469, 1983-1985 (Box 45)
  - 5470 - 5515, 1983-1985 (Box 46)
  - 5518 - 5560, 1983-1985 (Box 47)
  - 5563 - 5610, 1983-1985 (Box 48)
  - 5611 - 5672, 1983-1985 (Box 49)
  - 5674 - 5720, 1985-1988 (Box 50)
  - 5720 - 5750, 1985-1988 (Box 51)
  - 5751 - 5792, 1985-1988 (Box 52)
  - 5792 - 5822, 1985-1988 (Box 53)
  - 5825 - 5851, 1985-1988 (Box 54)
  - 5852 - 5879, 1985-1988 (Box 55)
  - 5880 - 5907, 1985-1988 (Box 56)
  - 5907 - 5941, 1985-1988 (Box 57)
  - 5943 - 5981, 1985-1988 (Box 58)
  - 5983 - 6016, 1985-1988 (Box 59)
  - 6019 - 6063, 1985-1988 (Box 60)
  - 6063 - 6091, 5500, 5584, 1985-1988 (Box 61)
  - 6092 - 6122, 1985-1988 (Box 62)
  - 6123 - 6160, 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - 6161 - 6201, 1988-1989 (Box 64)
  - 6203 - 6235, 1988-1989 (Box 65)
  - 6236 - 6279, 1988-1989 (Box 66)
  - 6282-6310, 5447-5449, 5906, 5996, 1988-1989 (Box 67)
  - 6311 - 6348, 1989-1990 (Box 68)
  - 6348 - 6391, 1989-1990 (Box 69)
  - 6397 - 6432, 1989-1990 (Box 70)
  - 6432 - 6466, 1989-1990 (Box 71)
  - 6466 - 6501, 1989-1990 (Box 72)
  - 6502 - 6539, 1989-1990 (Box 73)
  - 6541 - 6578, 1990-1991 (Box 74)
  - 6579 - 6618, 1990-1991 (Box 75)
  - 6619 - 6649, 1990-1991 (Box 76)
  - 6650 - 6685, 1992 (Box 77)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2018
  - 6686 - 6720, 1992 (Box 78)
  - 6721- 6757, 1992 (Box 79)
  - 6760 - 6788, 1992 (Box 80)
  - 6789 - 6833, 1992 (Box 81)
  - 6834 - 6873, 1993 (Box 82)
    Restricted - Open in 2019
  - 6874 - 6911, 1993 (Box 83)
  - 6912 - 6952, 1993 (Box 84)
  - 6954 - 7008, 1994 (Box 85)
    Restricted - Open in 2020
  - 7016 - 7077, 1994 (Box 86)
  - 5999, 6368, 6371, 6373, 6392, 6892, 6947, 6963-7021, 1994 (Box 87)
  - 7064 - 7097, 1994 (Box 88)
  - 7098 - 7144, 1995 (Box 89)
    Restricted - Open in 2021
  - 7145 - 7184, 1995 (Box 90)
  - 7189 - 7238, 1996 (Box 91)
    Restricted - Open in 2022
  - 7240 - 7298, 1996 (Box 92)
  - 7300 - 7404, 1996 (Box 93)
- Correspondence Concerning Manuscripts, 1953-2000; 2
  Scope and Contents
  Often includes general correspondence as well as editorial correspondence. Files in the 1990s-2000 may include various versions of the manuscript.
  - Rejected Manuscripts, 1953-1964 (Box 94)
  - Rejected Manuscripts, 1965-1966 (Box 95)
  - Accepted Manuscripts, 1964-1965 (Box 95)
  - Accepted Manuscripts, 1965-1966 (Box 96)
  - 5225 - 5298, 1982-1983 (Box 97)
  - 5299 - 5357, 1982-1983 (Box 98)
  - 5358 - 5437, 1983 (Box 99)
  - 5437 - 5497, 1983-1984 (Box 100)
  - 5498 - 5580, 1984 (Box 101)
  - 5581 - 5652, 1984-1985 (Box 102)
  - 5653 - 5718, 1985-1986 (Box 103)
  - 5719 - 5786, 1985-1986 (Box 104)
  - 5787 - 5850, 1985-1987 (Box 105)
  - 5851 - 5903, 1986-1987 (Box 106)
  - 5903 - 5953, 1986-1987 (Box 107)
  - 5953 - 6002, 1987-1988 (Box 108)
  - 6003 - 6063, 1987-1988 (Box 109)
  - 6064 - 6112, 1987-1988 (Box 110)
  - 6113 - 6176, 1988 (Box 111)
  - 6177 - 6241, 1988-1989 (Box 112)
  - 6242 - 6304, 1988-1989 (Box 113)
  - 6305 - 6369, 1989 (Box 114)
  - 6370 - 6439, 1989-1990 (Box 115)
  - 6440 - 6493, 1990 (Box 116)
  - 6494 - 6559, 1990 (Box 117)
  - 6560 - 6612, 1990-1991 (Box 118)
  - 6613 - 6674, 1991 (Box 119)
  - 6675 - 6722, 1991-1992 (Box 120)
  - 6723 - 6779, 1992 (Box 121)
  - 6780 - 6835, 1992 (Box 122)
  - 6838 - 6894, 1993 (Box 123)
  - 6895 - 6958, 1993 (Box 124)
  - 6959-6999. 6119-6615, 1993 (Box 125)
  - 6634-6998, 7000-7029, 1993-1994 (Box 126)
  - 7030 - 7099, 1994 (Box 127)
  - 7100 - 7178, 1994-1995 (Box 128)
  - 7179 - 7246, 1995 (Box 129)
  - 7247 - 7319, 1995-1996 (Box 130)
  - 7320 - 7365, 1996 (Box 131)
  - 7366 - 7405, 1996 (Box 132)
  - 7406 - 7440, 1996 (Box 133)
  - 7441 - 7468, 1996 (Box 134)
  - 7469 - 7501, 1996-1997 (Box 135)
    Restricted - Open in 2023
  - 7502 - 7536, 1997 (Box 136)
  - 7537 - 7565, 1997 (Box 137)
  - 7566 - 7595, 1997 (Box 138)
  - 7596 - 7620, 1997 (Box 139)
  - 7621 - 7672, 1997 (Box 140)
  - 7673 - 7703, 1998 (Box 141)
    Restricted - Open in 2024
  - 7704 - 7730, 1998 (Box 142)
  - 7731 - 7764, 1998 (Box 143)
  - 7765 - 7794, 1998 (Box 144)
  - 7795 - 7821, 1998 (Box 145)
  - 7822 - 7862, 1998 (Box 146)
  - 7863 - 7892, 1998 (Box 147)
  - 7893 - 7930, 1998-1999 (Box 148)
    Restricted - Open in 2025
  - 7931 - 7964, 1999 (Box 149)
  - 7965 - 7997, 1999 (Box 150)
  - 7998 - 8030, 1999 (Box 151)
  - 8031 - 8075, 1999 (Box 152)
  - 8076 - 8105, 1999 (Box 153)
  - 8106 - 8139, 1999 (Box 154)
  - 8140 - 8168, 1999-2000 (Box 155)
    Restricted - Open in 2026
  - 8169 - 8206, 2000 (Box 156)